<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<catalog>
	<serie>
		<title>House of The Dragon</title>
		<cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjBiOGIyY2YtOTA3OC00YzY1LThkYjktMGRkYTNhNTExY2I2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTEyMjM2NDc2._V1_FMjpg_UX1013_.jpg</cover-url>
		<year>2022</year>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<numberOfVotes>142000</numberOfVotes>
		<pgRating>TV-MA</pgRating>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<summaryOfSerie>An internal succession war within House Targaryen at the height of its power, 172 years before the birth of Daenerys Targaryen.</summaryOfSerie>
		<star>Paddy Considine</star>
		<star>Matt Smith</star>
		<star>Rhys Ifans</star>
		<actor>Fabien Frankel</actor>
		<actor>Bill Paterson</actor>
		<actor>Gavin Spokes</actor>
		<actor>Eve Best</actor>
		<actor>Graham McTavish</actor>
		<creator>Ryan J. Condal</creator>
		<creator>George R. R. Martin</creator>
		<director>Clare Kilner</director>
		<director>Miguel Sapochnik</director>
		<director>Alan Taylor</director>
		<writer>Ryan J. Condal</writer>
		<writer>George R.R. Martin</writer>
		<writer>Sara Hess</writer>
		<numberOfSeasons>1</numberOfSeasons>
		<season >
			<episode >
				<title>The Heirs of the Dragon</title>
				<description>Viserys hosts a tournament to celebrate the birth of his second child. Rhaenyra welcomes her uncle Daemon back to the Red Keep.</description>
				<duration>1h6m</duration>
				<review>Nice start to an opening series. Definitely had my attention from the beginning to the end. Remember, this is a marathon, not a sprint. This episode laid down a great foundation for episodes to come.</review>
				<review>The premiere of House Of The Dragon was stunning in cinematography while also keeping the same energy as GOT, overall this show will definitely make amends for the devastating goodbye we gave to Game Of Thrones. I cant wait for this new adventure, as it's only just begun.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>The Rogue Prince</title>
				<description>Rhaenyra oversteps at the Small Council. Viserys is urged to secure the succession through marriage. Daemon announces his intentions.</description>
				<duration>54min</duration>
				<review>I found episode 2 to be a slower episode. Not all bad but more strategic in laying the pieces of the story and context. The slower pace allowed us to settle into this time and world a bit more and get to know the new players of this realm a little more. It is not as strong as its first episode but still quite decent. The writing, adaptation and dialogue seem strong. We see a King struggling to make the best decisions he can for himself, his daughter and the realm. Meanwhile the rebellious brother is being difficult. Matt Smith is excellent and seems a natural fit for this role. I feel this show still has potential to be great.</review>
				<review>It was ok. Not gonna say it was boring or inconsequential but maybe some of the issues were not fully developed as far as I am concerned. I'd say it was quite lame for me and although the finale of the episode was a perfect clickbait for number three. Hope next one has way more action and less conversation so I can help yawning from time to time. And I still think the resemblance of Game of Thrones is even more obvious. And now as the review must go up to six hundred characters I'll keep writing about costume design, photography, production, visual effects (they're great regarding the way dragons are displayed on screen).</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Second of His Name</title>
				<description>Daemon and the Sea Snake battle the Crabfeeder. The realm celebrates Aegon's second nameday. Rhaenyra faces the prospect of marriage.</description>
				<duration>1h3m</duration>
				<review>The politics and family drama is very intricate and intriguing. The same can not be said about the big battle sequence. It's very well made and it looks phenomenal but it's way too predictable which honestly makes it underwhelming. Spectacular things happen on the screen but there is no tension or stakes which makes it kinda meh. A good fight scene is only as good as the writing. It is still a great episode. The relationships are very intricate and it's understandable why every character acts the way they do. Everyone has their own agenda and they can't please anyone without hurting someone else they care about. The ancient norms and rules are questioned and the discussions regarding duty and love are thought-provoking and interesting. The stakes are immense and the air is full of tension.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>King of the Narrow Sea</title>
				<description>Rhaenyra continues her search for a suitable match, Daemon returns to Kings Landing and stirs more trouble for the King. Rhaenyra learns a valuable lesson.</description>
				<duration>1h03m</duration>
				<review>What an amazing episode, to even think that there is innocent character in the world that George R. R. Martin created will be an absurdity. You see, everyone and I literally mean everyone even the characters we love and support seek their own benefit even if it means lying, deceiving and even cheating to get what they want.</review>
				<review>What an amazing way to put the pieces in places for the upcoming fight for the throne. The characters are so sly in fighting for the throne, it's just bafflingly good writing that I never seen before even in the original GOT.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>We Light the Way</title>
				<description>Daemon visits his wife in the Vale. Viserys and Rhaenyra broker agreements with the Velaryons. Alicent seeks the truth about the princess.</description>
				<duration>59m</duration>
				<review>Now I get it. Bot reviewers are driving the score up, 9.9 before it finishes!!?? HBO must have been worried that it was going to be tainted by the stench of Game of Thrones season's 7 and 8, or that God awful Lord of the rings nonsense. HOD is way better than those seasons but not as good as season's 1-5 GOT. The plot is still very good, Daemon is still a great character, well acted by Matt Smith although he is teleporting all over Westeros to kill his wife. Rhys ifans, still good as Otto. And Paddy Considine still good as the King. The wedding was handled badly. Why was the Knight of kisses killed? Why were they married immediately afterward? The scene on the boat when Crispin asks Rhaenarys to run away was silly.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>The Princess and the Queen</title>
				<description>Ten years later. Rhaenyra navigates Alicent's continued speculation about her children, while Daemon and Laena weigh an offer in Pentos.</description>
				<duration>59m</duration>
				<review>Missing Milly Alcock and Theo Nate! They were one of the reason to watch. Let's see what the older characters have to offer. Thanks goodness Sir Christian is still here, being played by the same person!!!!! The show is still well with the time to continue watch, just missing certain folks. Guess I'll wait and watch to see the end results. The dragons are the best part of the show. The queen has turned into a completely different person, just jealous that she doesn't have a living relationship of love and respect. And there is no real as tionship between her and Rhyenyran. Be more concern about herself and hers sons.</review>
			</episode>
		</season>
	</serie>
	<serie>
		<title>The Wheel of Time</title>
		<cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzA2Nzk5M2EtNWY4Yi00ZDY4LThkZTgtYjhhNWEyMGY0MjFjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkxNjUyNQ@@._V1_.jpg</cover-url>
		<year>2021</year>
		<score>7.1</score>
		<numberOfVotes>102000</numberOfVotes>
		<pgRating>TV-14</pgRating>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<summaryOfSerie>Set in a high fantasy world where magic exists, but only some can access it, a woman named Moiraine crosses paths with five young men and women. This sparks a dangerous, world-spanning journey. Based on the book series by Robert Jordan.</summaryOfSerie>
		<star>Rosamund Pike</star>
		<star>Daniel Henney</star>
		<star>Madeleine Madden</star>
		<actor>Zoe Robins</actor>
		<actor>Josha Stradowski</actor>
		<actor>Marcus Rutherford</actor>
		<actor>Kate Fleetwood</actor>
		<actor>Priyanka Bose</actor>
		<creator>Rafe Judkins</creator>
		<director>Uta Brisewitz</director>
		<director>Ciaran Donnelly</director>
		<director>Wayne Yip</director>
		<writer>Robert Jordan</writer>
		<writer>Paul Clarkson</writer>
		<writer>Michael Clarkson</writer>
		<numberOfSeasons>1</numberOfSeasons>
		<season >
			<episode >
				<title>Leavetaking</title>
				<description>A strange noblewoman arrives in a remote mountain village, claiming one of five youths is the reincarnation of an ancient power who once destroyed the world and will do so again, if she's not able to discover which of them it is. But they all have less time than they think.</description>
				<duration>54m</duration>
				<review>The casting is just bad. Only one remotely accurate is Rand. Even Mat is not very good, Lan is probably the worst of all. Three Rivers women are completely wrong also, there was plenty of diversity in Jordan's books without the need to change entire characters.</review>
				<review>I'm a huge fan of the series. I think I've read all of them at least 3 times. Acting was good as were special effects. My only criticism is that they made it a little dark. Mostly the tone...but also the lighting.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Shadow's Waiting</title>
				<description>Moiraine and Lan lead the four villagers to safety, unsure which is the one from the prophecy. But the friends are equally unsure about their rescuers, especially once they see how far Moiraine is willing to go for her mission and how far astray Lan is willing to lead them.</description>
				<duration>57m</duration>
				<review>The first episode was a bit clunky, but this one really nails it. Love seeing these characters come to life. Looking forward to more. And for the haters to disappear, which they will eventually.</review>
				<review>Opening scene was great. The whitecloaks are super creepy here. This is a big improvement on episode one. Much better paced, the opening and ending scenes were brilliant and everything is moving forwards at a good pace. I hope they can keep this up for a full season. Barney Harris as Mat is particularly good in my opinion.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode>
				<title>A Place of Safety</title>
				<description>Moiraine and Lan find help in an unexpected - and unwanted - quarter, as the separated villagers try to find their way back to each other, or at least to refuge. But they all soon learn how far the Dark One's reach extends.</description>
				<duration>58m</duration>
				<review>I've read all the books, love them. Glad to see the same character elements shine through in the show. Happy to see that the show embraces the nature of the many nations and people of the books. I had quite a few laughs from Mat's smart ass remarks and Nynaeve's bravery and ferocity. Looking forward to the rest of the episodes!</review>
				<review>So detailed and laying character traits while leading towards some amazing storylines! This is an excellent episode. As the focus continues with the Two Rivers being left further and further behind. Really enjoyed every second and we get introduced to new fun groups!</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>The Dragon Reborn</title>
				<description>Moiraine struggles with uncertainty while Lan struggles with their new companion. Rand wonders about Mat. Egwene and Perrin take their first steps down a different path. An incredible new power is unleashed on the world.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>First half of the episode had many of the problems the third one had. Second half absolutely blew me away. The last few sequences were some of the best things I've seen from a fantasy show.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode>
				<title>Blood Calls Blood</title>
				<description>Perrin and Egwene run into a familiar face. Mat and Rand see strange ones. Moiraine and Lan mourn their loss.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>Episode four is still my favorite -- for very biased reasons -- but episode five is a solid addition to the series so far. A number of wonderful Easter eggs for book readers, a small glimpse into the politics at the White Tower, and some much needed humanization of a character too many book readers misunderstand as completely stoic to the point of being nearly without emotion.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>The Flame of Tar Valon</title>
				<description>Moiraine faces the consequences of her actions. Mat faces the darkness in himself. Egwene faces the most powerful woman in the world.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>Writing on this episode and a few prior is just plain poor. It's fan fiction level, and not the good kind. We'd expect that anyone who decides to stray from the books would have both skill and reason for doing that. But there's no skill and no reason to be found in this adaption.</review>
			</episode>
		</season>
	</serie>
	<serie>
		<title>The Witcher</title>
		<cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2FiOWU4YzYtMzZiOS00MzcyLTlkOGEtOTgwZmEwMzAxMzA3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkxNjUyNQ@@._V1_.jpg</cover-url>
		<year>2019</year>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<numberOfVotes>483000</numberOfVotes>
		<pgRating>TV-MA</pgRating>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<summaryOfSerie>Geralt of Rivia, a solitary monster hunter, struggles to find his place in a world where people often prove more wicked than beasts.</summaryOfSerie>
		<star>Henry Cavill</star>
		<star>Freya Allan</star>
		<star>Anya Chalotra</star>
		<actor>Eamon Farren</actor>
		<actor>Wilson Mbomio</actor>
		<actor>Joey Batey</actor>
		<actor>Tom Canton</actor>
		<actor>Mimi Ndiweni</actor>
		<creator>Lauren Schmidt</creator>
		<director>Alik Sakharov</director>
		<director>Stephen Surjik</director>
		<director>Charlotte Brändström</director>
		<writer>Andrzej Sapkowski</writer>
		<writer>Lauren Schmidt</writer>
		<writer>Matthew D'Ambrosio</writer>
		<writer>Haily Hall</writer>
		<numberOfSeasons>2</numberOfSeasons>
		<season >
			<episode >
				<title>The End's Beginning</title>
				<description>Hostile townsfolk and a cunning mage greet Geralt in the town of Blaviken. Ciri finds her royal world upended when Nilfgaard sets its sights on Cintra.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>I'm a player of the 1 and 2 games, 3 I have yet to start. That being said, I think this is a great introduction to the Witcher Universe. Action, story, humor, gore, and sex. It's all good. 10 / 10.</review>
				<review>So the Princess of the Fallen Empire is now on her journey to began her own Empire with the very protagonist of the series. I totally enjoyed the episode especially the quick set-up it provided to this series. The action scenes very really good and I will surely highlight the ending fight of this episode.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Four Marks</title>
				<description>Bullied and neglected, Yennefer accidentally finds a means of escape. Geralt's hunt for a so-called devil goes to hell. Ciri seeks safety in numbers.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>What was missing from the first episode you essentially get here. More backstory, more storytelling makes it a more watchable episode than the first one. While the first one lacked in story, but great action, this one does the opposite.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Betrayer Moon</title>
				<description>Geralt takes on another Witcher's unfinished business in a kingdom stalked by a ferocious beast. At a brutal cost, Yennefer forges a magical new future.</description>
				<duration>1h7m</duration>
				<review>Geralt and the strigga was my favorite in the Last Wish book. I'm glad to see how it was adapted and I loved it all. There were some deviations but overall...I love this episode and this show.</review>
				<review>I extremely enjoyed the striga story which hooked me to the games as of the beginning!! Great and unexpected enjoyment of this show!!</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Of Banquets, Bastards and Burials</title>
				<description>Against his better judgment, Geralt accompanies Jaskier to a royal ball. Ciri wanders into an enchanted forest. Yennefer tries to protect her charges.</description>
				<duration>1h2m</duration>
				<review>Awesome, simply awesome! To those, who at least played Witcher in Sapkowski's deep and brilliant universe, the law of surprise couldnt be visualized better. How wonderful was that, brilliant. I still can not pick up my jaw from the floor. Wonderful piece of interpretation and fulfilment to the saga.</review>
			</episode>
		</season>
		<season >
			<episode >
				<title>A Grain of Truth</title>
				<description>Geralt sets off with Ciri on a journey that leads him to an old friend. After the battle of Sodden, Tissaia shows no mercy in her search of information.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>Good start to a new season. Ciri getting more character and geralt top as always. Sidestory a bit too long in comparison to the main ending on the last season.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>A Grain of Truth</title>
				<description>Seeking a safe place for Ciri, Geralt heads for home, but danger lurks everywhere - even Kaer Morhen. Yennefer's dreams could be the key to her freedom.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>This episode feels like the writers didn't understand the characters. The changes in the story and characters are a big middle finger for fans of the books and games. What is this plot? Key elements of the basic story are missing or get changed. This is so frustrating...</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>What Is Lost</title>
				<description>Impatient with Geralt's methods, Ciri braves major obstacles to prove her mettle. Scheming and suspicion among the Brotherhood make Yennefer a target.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>The witcher was special and unique, and people liked it for that matter.. now they're turning this into some game of throne, but bad.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>What Is Lost</title>
				<description>A guest at Kaer Morhen extends a guiding hand to Ciri - and an invitation to Geralt. On the run in Redania, Yennefer seeks safety below ground.</description>
				<duration>59m</duration>
				<review>This episode was a bit confusing, a lot going on and a lot of concepts introduced. However, what I did understand was pretty good. One great reference to season ones dual timelines.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode>
				<title>What Is Lost</title>
				<description>A guest at Kaer Morhen extends a guiding hand to Ciri - and an invitation to Geralt. On the run in Redania, Yennefer seeks safety below ground.</description>
				<duration>59m</duration>
				<review>This episode was a bit confusing, a lot going on and a lot of concepts introduced. However, what I did understand was pretty good. One great reference to season ones dual timelines.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Turn Your Back</title>
				<description>As a powerful mage joins the hunt for Ciri, she cuts a deal with Vesemir over his extraordinary discovery. Geralt explores the mystery of the monoliths.</description>
				<duration>56m</duration>
				<review>A key Witcher characteristic - one that's established quite early in the show - is that they can't feel emotions.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Dear Friend...</title>
				<description>A close friend is lost - and another found - as Geralt helps Ciri learn more about her power. Cahir warns Fringilla to focus on their primary mission.</description>
				<duration>57m</duration>
				<review>It's all starting to come together, thankfully the show doled out some much needed answers. But still in need of a few more key pieces. Great acting and some good plot moves.</review>
			</episode>
		</season>
	</serie>
	<serie>
		<title>The Crown</title>
		<cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmNjYmI0OWItN2VkZi00NWQ5LWI0MzUtMjE4MzU0NDhmZjc4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjY0Mzk3NzA@._V1_FMjpg_UX1000_.jpg</cover-url>
		<year>2016</year>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<numberOfVotes>204019</numberOfVotes>
		<pgRating>TV-MA</pgRating>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<genre>History</genre>
		<summaryOfSerie>Follows the political rivalries and romance of Queen Elizabeth II's reign and the events that shaped the second half of the twentieth century.</summaryOfSerie>
		<star>Claire Foy</star>
		<star>Olivia Coleman</star>
		<star>Imelda Staunton</star>
		<star>Matt Smith</star>
		<star>Tobias Menzies</star>
		<actor>Jonathan Pryce</actor>
		<actor>Lesley Manville</actor>
		<actor>Dominic West</actor>
		<actor>Helena Bonham Carter</actor>
		<actor>Marion Bailey</actor>
		<creator>Peter Morgan</creator>
		<director>Benjamin Caron</director>
		<director>Philip Martin</director>
		<director>Jessica Hobbs</director>
		<director>Paul Whittington</director>
		<writer>Peter Morgan</writer>
		<writer>Edward Hemming</writer>
		<writer>Jonathan Wilson</writer>
		<writer>Tom Edge</writer>
		<numberOfSeasons>4</numberOfSeasons>
		<season >
			<episode >
				<title>Wolferton Splash</title>
				<description>A young Princess Elizabeth marries Prince Philip. As King George VI's health worsens, Winston Churchill becomes Prime Minister for the second time.</description>
				<duration>56m</duration>
				<review>Excellent start of a great story telling. This first episode got us as a audience. Constantly thinking about the great choice with the cast in this series.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Hyde Park Corner</title>
				<description>With King George too ill to travel, Elizabeth and Phillip embark on a four-continent Commonwealth tour. Party leaders attempt to undermine Churchill.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>Beyond of thinking this is actually a series, people got very concentrate in the plot. How can everything go down with a death and how can a young woman start her duty in life.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Windsor</title>
				<description>With Elizabeth in a new role, Phillip tries to assert some power. Churchill wants to delay the coronation. King George's disgraced brother arrives.</description>
				<duration>59m</duration>
				<review>The casting of John Lithgow for Winston was terrible. Not realistic at all. I can'tbelieve that a British actor to play that part better could not be found.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Act of God</title>
				<description>When dense fog cripples London for days and creates a serious health hazard, Churchill's inaction leaves him vulnerable to his political enemies.</description>
				<duration>57m</duration>
				<review>I come to this show not because I want to learn but because I just want to watch a good tv show. I don't automatically relate the characters to their real - life counterparts. These people in the Crown are fictional for all I care. Anyways, the cinematography of this thing just improves every single episode. They do several interesting camera sequences and that is appreciated. A solid episode.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Fagan</title>
				<description>As Thatcher's policies create rising unemployment, a desperate man breaks into the palace, where he finds Elizabeth's bedroom and awakens her for a talk.</description>
				<duration>57m</duration>
				<review>A wild episode for sure, that someone broke into the royal palace twice and managed to have six uninterrupted minutes with the queen. Good acting and an awesomely true storyline.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Terra Nullius</title>
				<description>On a tour of Australia, Diana struggles to balance motherhood with her royal duties while both she and Charles cope with their marriage difficulties.</description>
				<duration>57m</duration>
				<review>Oh Diana, looking for love in all the wrong places. A great episode in terms of storyline and acting.</review>
			</episode>
		</season>
		<season >
			<episode>
				<title>Misadventure</title>
				<description>As Philip leaves for a long tour, Elizabeth makes an upsetting discovery. Prime Minister Eden wants to strike back after Egypt seizes the Suez Canal.</description>
				<duration>56m</duration>
				<review>Great introduction to a new season, it explores and shows details of the crisis with Egypt.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>A Company of Men</title>
				<description>Elizabeth feels disconnected from Philip. Eden copes with international pressure and ill health. An interview stirs up harrowing memories for Philip.</description>
				<duration>56m</duration>
				<review>This episode is dedicated to the adventures of Phillip and the boys' club on their commonwealth tour. However, rather than focusing solely on Phillip's perspective, the episode examines its overall impact by looking at it through the lens of every story-line, depicting both the negative and positive aspects. We see the misogyny, racism, civic injustice, and scandal involved but also the valour, fun, and brotherhood. As in real life, we are shown the good and the bad, then forced to make the moral judgment ourselves.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Lisbon</title>
				<description>Palace insiders try to prevent a scandal that could reflect poorly on Philip. Eden faces censure from his cabinet and the press.</description>
				<duration>56m</duration>
				<review>Eventually the whole divorce situation has to be dealt with, and, in the end, the Royals are going to come out on top. Philip throws his friend to the wolves, but he really has no choice. The implications are too great. We get a look at the case of Anthony Eden as he faces his cabinet, which has been holding things together while he has been in the Bahamas.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Beryl</title>
				<description>When Elizabeth and Philip throw a grand party for their 10th anniversary, both Margaret and the new Prime Minister experience romantic tribulations.</description>
				<duration>1h</duration>
				<review>I find Princess Margaret to be a very sad character. She has to constantly play second fiddle to the Queen and to the Queen Mum. She loved someone but her station prevented her from doing anything about it. So she has become the free spirited (naughty) child. In this one we meet the notorious photographer that captured world news, Anthony Armstrong Jones (Great Name) who because of his caustic nature, attracts Margaret.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode>
				<title>Marionettes</title>
				<description>After Elizabeth makes a tone-deaf speech at a Jaguar factory, she and the monarchy come under public attack by an outspoken lord.</description>
				<duration>1h</duration>
				<review>It was great to see more development to Elizabeth, after seeing previous Season 2 episodes focusing on other characters (for instance Phillip, which could have been done better, and Margaret, which showed a vast improvement over how she was written the previous season). It was also great to see a supporting character so fully fleshed out in so little time in a way not done this well before in the previous episodes of 'The Crown'.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Vergangenheit</title>
				<description>A secret World War II document opens Elizabeth's eyes to grim realities about a family member. The Duke of Windsor campaigns to re-enter public life.</description>
				<duration>1h1m</duration>
				<review>For the first half of this episode, I thought that it was following two unrelated plots; the uncovering of damning documents from the Second World War and the return of David the exiled former king as he searches for work. However, midway through the episode it becomes clear that David is linked to the documents, and that their fallout will determine whether or not he is successful. As a result, what initially seemed like an episode of odds and ends actually dovetails neatly into a single conflict, and a powerful dilemma for Elizabeth.</review>
			</episode>
		</season>
	</serie>
	<serie>
		<title>The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power</title>
		<cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTg3NjcxYzgtYjljNC00Y2I2LWE3YmMtOTliZTkwYTE1MmZiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTY4NDc5MDE@._V1_FMjpg_UX1080_.jpg</cover-url>
		<year>2022</year>
		<score>6.9</score>
		<numberOfVotes>243219</numberOfVotes>
		<pgRating>Tv-14</pgRating>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<summaryOfSerie>Epic drama set thousands of years before the events of J.R.R. Tolkien's 'The Hobbit' and 'The Lord of the Rings' follows an ensemble cast of characters, both familiar and new, as they confront the long-feared re-emergence of evil to Middle-earth.</summaryOfSerie>
		<star>Morfydd Clark</star>
		<star>Ismael Cruz Cordova</star>
		<star>Charlie Vickers</star>
		<star>Markella Kavenagh</star>
		<star>Megan Richards</star>
		<actor>Daniel Weyman</actor>
		<actor>Lenny Henry</actor>
		<actor>Lenny Henry</actor>
		<actor>Sara Zwangobani</actor>
		<actor>Alex Tarrant</actor>
		<creator>John D. Payne</creator>
		<creator>Patrick McKay</creator>
		<director>Wayne Yip</director>
		<director>J.A. Bayona</director>
		<director>Charlotte Brändström</director>
		<writer>J.R.R. Tolkien</writer>
		<writer>Jason Cahill</writer>
		<writer>Patrick McKay</writer>

    <numberOfSeasons>1</numberOfSeasons>
		<season >
			<episode >
				<title>A Shadow of the Past</title>
				<description>Galadriel is disturbed by signs of an ancient evil's return. Arondir makes an unsettling discovery. Elrond is presented with an intriguing new venture. Nori breaks a deeply held community rule.</description>
				<duration>1h5m</duration>
				<review>Starts off well enough and the opening felt somewhat similar to Peter Jackson's FotR. Excellent visuals and you can tell the sets were very carefully selected and built. The cinematography is very well executed, but some of the action sequences felt a little strange specifically in the snow cave. Acting seemed a little wanting, but hopefully that I don't dwell on that the whole time. Lots of setup so I hope there's more meat later on but overall a decent start that I think Peter Jackson fans could appreciate.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode>
				<title>Adrift</title>
				<description>Galadriel finds a new ally. Elrond faces a cold reception from an old friend. Nori endeavors to help a Stranger. Arondir searches for answers while Bronwyn warns her people of a threat.</description>
				<duration>1h7m</duration>
				<review>Adrift is a better episode than the choppy first, it is paced better, acted a little better and sets up the story going forwards. Like episode one, Nori is still the highlight so far, and I though the scenes with Elrond and Durin were pretty funny and well done. The scenes in Khazad-dûm were the best part of this episode, and they very much felt like they belonged in the Hobbit Trilogy. The sets and quality of the visuals during these scenes were fantastic, so props to the guys responsible for carrying these few episodes.</review>
				<review>Adrift was just fine, not great, not bad. I do hope the episodes get better going forwards, but I think Amazon should have released 3 episodes instead of 2, because I'm still not invested in these characters or the story.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Adar</title>
				<description>Arondir finds himself a captive. Galadriel and Halbrand explore a legendary kingdom. Elendil is given a new assignment. Nori faces the consequences.</description>
				<duration>1h9m</duration>
				<review>You have Middle Earth and you don't know what to do with it. You have unbelievably high budget and you give me this CGI. Also the main character is just unlikeable and not because she is a woman but because she is so arrogant and she treats everyone with disrespect. And the harfoots are so out of place and forced in to the show just so you can have something that reminded us of the hobbits.</review>
				<review>Overall solid third episode. With some breathtaking cinematography, beautiful soundtracks, and an interesting plot.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>The Great Wave</title>
				<description>Queen Regent Míriel's faith is tested. Isildur finds himself at a crossroads. Elrond uncovers a secret. Arondir is given an ultimatum. Theo disobeys Bronwyn.</description>
				<duration>1h11m</duration>
				<review>Episode 4 of Rings of Power is actually pretty great, for the most part. Like previous episodes, the dialogue and acting is very average and the story is muddled and confused. We are now 4 episodes in - 4 hours of screentime and yet the story is still barely progressing, I feel like at times I'm watching something pointless.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Queen Regent Míriel's faith is tested. Isildur finds himself at a crossroads. Elrond uncovers a secret. Arondir is given an ultimatum. Theo disobeys Bronwyn.</title>
				<description>Nori questions her instincts; Elrond struggles to stay true to his oath; Halbrand weighs his destiny; The Southlanders brace for attack.</description>
				<duration>1h12m</duration>
				<review>Just seeing the first 20 minutes of this episode, really brought me back to the time that Lord of the Rings was everything to me.</review>
				<review>The entire season seems to be aimed at introducing the characters. Too bad that 90% of the characters are either dull or annoying. Since the story has many branches, not all of them have been sufficiently developed in this episode.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode>
				<title>Udûn</title>
				<description>Adar and his army march on Ostirith.</description>
				<duration>1h9m</duration>
				<review>I haven't minded the series up until now, but I have been yearning for a great fight scene/battle. In this episode we get that and more. I was honestly on the edge of my seat and when I checked the run time expecting the episode to finish there was still 25 minutes left of the episode. The story is still quite messy, with a few plot lines not making much sense and alot of things happen by chance. But Im willing to ignore these negatives with the fight scenses in this episode and some of the choreography. The music was brilliant this episode, it really captured the lord of the rings feelings that the series has missed. The ending was fantastic too, I honestly can't wait until the next episode. 9/10, I hope the next two episodes are as action packed as this one.</review>
			</episode>
		</season>
	</serie>
	<serie>
		<title>Stranger Things</title>
		<cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYmE0NDY4ZjAtZDM2Ni00NzFhLThkZTgtMjgyMGU4OTVmNDYxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTIzNDk1MDYz._V1_.jpg</cover-url>
		<year>2016</year>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<numberOfVotes>1160764</numberOfVotes>
		<pgRating>TV-16</pgRating>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<genre>Fantasy</genre>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
		<summaryOfSerie>When a young boy disappears, his mother, a police chief and his friends must confront terrifying supernatural forces in order to get him back.</summaryOfSerie>
		<star>Millie Bobby Brown</star>
		<star>Finn Wolfhard</star>
		<star>Caleb McLaughlin</star>
		<actor>Winona Ryder</actor>
		<actor>Natalia Dyer</actor>
		<actor>Gaten Matarazzo</actor>
		<actor>Charlie Heaton</actor>
		<creator>Matt Duffer</creator>
		<creator>Ross Duffer</creator>
		<director>Matt Duffer</director>
		<director>Ross Duffer</director>
		<director>Shawn Levy</director>
		<writer>Matt Duffer</writer>
		<writer>Ross Duffer</writer>
		<writer>Paul Dichter</writer>
		<writer>Kate Trefry</writer>
    <numberOfSeasons>4</numberOfSeasons>
		<season >
			<episode >
				<title>The Vanishing of Will Byers</title>
				<description>At the U.S. Dept. of Energy an unexplained event occurs. Then when a young Dungeons and Dragons playing boy named Will disappears after a night with his friends, his mother Joyce and the town of Hawkins are plunged into darkness.</description>
				<duration>47m</duration>
				<review>The first episode of "Stranger Things" does a good job of introducing the 'mystery' and the characters, but the direction, acting, pace and dialogue is just average.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode>
				<title>The Weirdo on Maple Street</title>
				<description>Mike hides the mysterious girl in his house. Joyce gets a strange phone call.</description>
				<duration>55m</duration>
				<review>The first focus of this episode is the strange girl, eleven (el for short) who is being hidden by the boys. She is obviously in danger, but the boys are afraid of the most basic things, like getting caught. It is revealed that this person, whatever she is, had telekinetic powers. She also can't seem to tell them anything that helps. It does appear that she knows who Will is. The search continues for the boy. Meanwhile, as Will's mother goes bonkers from worry, Will's brother keeps trying to figure things out. He even pays a visit to his father, but it is fruitless.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>Holly, Jolly</title>
				<description>An increasingly concerned Nancy looks for Barb and finds out what Jonathan's been up to. Joyce is convinced Will is trying to talk to her.</description>
				<duration>51m</duration>
				<review>Without doubt, "Holly, Jolly" is one of the most impactful episodes of this year. The range of emotions you feel from beginning to end leave you exhausted yet yearning to learn more about this small town fable.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode>
				<title>The Body</title>
				<description>Refusing to believe Will is dead, Joyce tries to connect with her son. The boys give Eleven a makeover. Jonathan and Nancy form an unlikely alliance.</description>
				<duration>49m</duration>
				<review>I never thought I'd be as into the show as I am, and there's a little part of me that's disappointed we've already reached the halfway mark. "The Body" is another winner; worthy performances, haunting imagery and a fantastic deepening mystery.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>The Flea and the Acrobat</title>
				<description>Refusing to believe Will is dead, Joyce tries to connect with her son. The boys give Eleven a makeover. Jonathan and Nancy form an unlikely alliance.</description>
				<duration>52m</duration>
				<review>Season 1 was a very promising first season to 'Stranger Things', and to me it's one of the show's better seasons. Of the previous four episodes only "Chapter Two: The Weirdo on Maple Street" disappointed a little while still being good. "Chapter Four: The Body" was especially outstanding, with everything that made the previous episodes as good as they were while executing the good things even better while managing to progress the plot.</review>
			</episode>
			<episode >
				<title>The Monster</title>
				<description>Hopper and Joyce find the truth about the lab's experiments. After their fight, the boys look for the missing Eleven.</description>
				<duration>46m</duration>
				<review>The Monster' is action packed thrilling episode that starts to draw the ring close. The episode is faster in pace, much more is going on, as for now we have very clear picture about all the important characters and their motives, what drives them. Some very important questions get the answers while some new mysteries open up. 'The Monster' uses may classic story development devices that some might find cliche, but these are crucially important to move the story forward.</review>
			</episode>
		</season>
	</serie>
</catalog>
